%, %
alpha: 100%
smooth: OFF
fadein/out: ,
align: OFF at LEFT TOP
time offset: 0
forced subs: OFF
palette: , fff, cccccc, 999999, 3333fa, 1111bb, fa3333, bb1111, 33fa33, 11bb11, fafa33, bbbb11, fa33fa, bb11bb, 33fafa, 11bbbb
custom colors: OFF, tridx: , colors: , 444444, 888888, cccccc
langidx: 0
id: en, index: 0
timestamp: ::28:153, filepos: 0
timestamp: ::43:710, filepos: 010
timestamp: ::48:298, filepos: 038
timestamp: ::56:306, filepos: 070
timestamp: ::59:268, filepos: 080
timestamp: :::478, filepos: 098
timestamp: ::04:106, filepos: 0b8
timestamp: ::10:821, filepos: 0d0
timestamp: ::15:367, filepos: 108
timestamp: ::21:665, filepos: 148
timestamp: ::25:586, filepos: 168
timestamp: ::27:629, filepos: 178
timestamp: ::34:636, filepos: 190
timestamp: ::37:431, filepos: 1b0
timestamp: ::40:517, filepos: 1c8
timestamp: ::45:105, filepos: 1f0
timestamp: ::48:317, filepos: 1f8
timestamp: ::51:862, filepos: 220
timestamp: ::55:657, filepos: 248
timestamp: ::58:869, filepos: 270
timestamp: :::871, filepos: 280
timestamp: ::03:248, filepos: 290
timestamp: ::07:919, filepos: 2a8
timestamp: ::12:549, filepos: 2c0
timestamp: ::15:177, filepos: 2e0
timestamp: ::18:347, filepos: 318
timestamp: ::24:811, filepos: 338
timestamp: ::28:940, filepos: 360
timestamp: ::33:528, filepos: 378
timestamp: ::36:865, filepos: 390
timestamp: ::39:951, filepos: 3a0
timestamp: ::42:537, filepos: 3b0
timestamp: ::46:458, filepos: 3b8
timestamp: ::49:878, filepos: 3c0
timestamp: ::53:298, filepos: 3d0
timestamp: ::57:928, filepos: 3e0
timestamp: :::847, filepos: 408
timestamp: :::475, filepos: 418
timestamp: ::10:691, filepos: 450
timestamp: ::13:527, filepos: 478
timestamp: ::15:529, filepos: 488
timestamp: ::18:490, filepos: 4a8
timestamp: ::25:205, filepos: 4c0
timestamp: ::27:749, filepos: 4c8
timestamp: ::34:256, filepos: 4e0
timestamp: ::36:842, filepos: 4f0
timestamp: ::41:972, filepos: 508
timestamp: ::44:641, filepos: 528
timestamp: ::48:353, filepos: 548
timestamp: ::51:148, filepos: 568
timestamp: ::54:276, filepos: 588
timestamp: ::57:821, filepos: 5b8
timestamp: :::073, filepos: 5d0
timestamp: ::02:075, filepos: 5e8
timestamp: ::20:260, filepos: 6
timestamp: ::27:642, filepos: 640
timestamp: ::30:020, filepos: 668
timestamp: ::32:230, filepos: 688
timestamp: ::38:069, filepos: 6a0
timestamp: ::41:114, filepos: 6d8
timestamp: ::44:075, filepos: 708
timestamp: ::47:037, filepos: 738
timestamp: ::49:039, filepos: 758
timestamp: ::51:249, filepos: 778
timestamp: ::54:419, filepos: 7a8
timestamp: ::56:379, filepos: 7c0
timestamp: ::59:090, filepos: 7e8
timestamp: ::03:553, filepos: 818
timestamp: :::472, filepos: 830
timestamp: ::08:558, filepos: 868
timestamp: ::11:520, filepos: 890
timestamp: ::13:438, filepos: 8b0
timestamp: ::25:742, filepos: 8e0
timestamp: ::29:871, filepos: 910
timestamp: ::36:670, filepos: 920
timestamp: ::39:506, filepos: 950
timestamp: ::42:425, filepos: 970
timestamp: ::45:3, filepos: 988
timestamp: ::50:851, filepos: 9a0
timestamp: ::53:436, filepos: 9c0
timestamp: ::54:938, filepos: 9d8
timestamp: ::57:190, filepos: 9f8
timestamp: ::58:9, filepos: a10
timestamp: :::902, filepos: a30
timestamp: ::03:196, filepos: a48
timestamp: ::05:574, filepos: a58
timestamp: ::08:285, filepos: a88
timestamp: ::11:162, filepos: aa8
timestamp: ::13:164, filepos: ac0
timestamp: ::15:667, filepos: ae8
timestamp: ::18:378, filepos: b
timestamp: ::21:6, filepos: b18
timestamp: ::23:8, filepos: b30
timestamp: ::25:343, filepos: b40
timestamp: ::29:723, filepos: b58
timestamp: ::31:725, filepos: b78
timestamp: ::34:561, filepos: b98
timestamp: ::36:855, filepos: bb8
timestamp: ::39:649, filepos: be8
timestamp: ::41:860, filepos: c10
timestamp: ::43:862, filepos: c30
timestamp: ::48:199, filepos: c60
timestamp: ::53:038, filepos: c88
timestamp: ::57:208, filepos: cc8
timestamp: ::03:381, filepos: cd8
timestamp: ::06:384, filepos: d
timestamp: ::09:095, filepos: d30
timestamp: ::11:640, filepos: d40
timestamp: ::20:273, filepos: d60
timestamp: ::24:444, filepos: d98
timestamp: ::28:657, filepos: dd0
timestamp: ::32:619, filepos: df8
timestamp: ::36:957, filepos: e10
timestamp: ::40:919, filepos: e38
timestamp: ::44:798, filepos: e58
timestamp: ::49:260, filepos: e78
timestamp: ::51:304, filepos: e98
timestamp: ::54:766, filepos: ec0
timestamp: ::57:811, filepos: ee0
timestamp: ::59:771, filepos: ef8
timestamp: ::04:025, filepos: f38
timestamp: :::363, filepos: f58
timestamp: ::11:825, filepos: f78
timestamp: ::14:911, filepos: fa8
timestamp: ::17:497, filepos: fb0
timestamp: ::19:958, filepos: fc8
timestamp: ::32:721, filepos: fe8
timestamp: ::34:848, filepos: ff8
timestamp: ::36:891, filepos: 01010
timestamp: ::38:977, filepos: 01038
timestamp: ::40:979, filepos: 01050
timestamp: ::44:065, filepos: 01078
timestamp: ::46:568, filepos: 01098
timestamp: ::50:488, filepos: 010c8
timestamp: ::53:116, filepos: 010f0
timestamp: ::56:327, filepos: 01110
timestamp: :::257, filepos: 01120
timestamp: ::12:3, filepos: 01140
timestamp: ::16:306, filepos: 01160
timestamp: ::18:933, filepos: 01178
timestamp: ::21:853, filepos: 01198
timestamp: ::25:190, filepos: 011b8
timestamp: ::27:817, filepos: 011d8
timestamp: ::30:570, filepos: 011f0
timestamp: ::33:698, filepos: 01210
timestamp: ::36:159, filepos: 01238
timestamp: ::38:953, filepos: 01268
timestamp: ::41:414, filepos: 01288
timestamp: ::44:334, filepos: 012b8
timestamp: ::49:5, filepos: 012e8
timestamp: ::51:633, filepos: 01310
timestamp: :::642, filepos: 01328
timestamp: ::02:644, filepos: 01348
timestamp: ::04:854, filepos: 01368
timestamp: ::08:983, filepos: 013a8
timestamp: ::11:111, filepos: 013c8
timestamp: ::13:696, filepos: 013e8
timestamp: ::16:074, filepos: 01418
timestamp: ::20:120, filepos: 01440
timestamp: ::24:415, filepos: 01468
timestamp: ::28:128, filepos: 01490
timestamp: ::30:922, filepos: 014b0
timestamp: ::33:7, filepos: 014c8
timestamp: ::36:594, filepos: 015
timestamp: ::42:183, filepos: 015
timestamp: ::44:978, filepos: 01540
timestamp: ::46:855, filepos: 01558
timestamp: ::49:482, filepos: 01578
timestamp: ::51:734, filepos: 01580
timestamp: ::57:615, filepos: 015b0
timestamp: ::59:951, filepos: 015d8
timestamp: ::04:080, filepos: 01610
timestamp: ::09:377, filepos: 01638
timestamp: ::12:797, filepos: 01658
timestamp: ::14:632, filepos: 01670
timestamp: ::16:676, filepos: 01680
timestamp: ::21:181, filepos: 016a0
timestamp: ::28:271, filepos: 016b8
timestamp: ::30:690, filepos: 016e0
timestamp: ::34:152, filepos: 01718
timestamp: ::37:488, filepos: 01750
timestamp: ::40:241, filepos: 01778
timestamp: ::43:745, filepos: 01788
timestamp: ::46:789, filepos: 01798
timestamp: ::48:791, filepos: 017c0
timestamp: ::52:337, filepos: 017e8
timestamp: ::55:215, filepos: 01810
timestamp: ::57:258, filepos: 01830
timestamp: :::637, filepos: 01850
timestamp: ::07:060, filepos: 01880
timestamp: ::09:520, filepos: 01888
timestamp: ::14:067, filepos: 018b8
timestamp: ::17:278, filepos: 018d8
timestamp: ::19:489, filepos: 018e8
timestamp: ::22:283, filepos: 01908
timestamp: ::26:537, filepos: 01930
timestamp: ::30:416, filepos: 01958
timestamp: ::33:169, filepos: 01970
timestamp: ::36:589, filepos: 01990
timestamp: ::40:218, filepos: 019c8
timestamp: ::42:345, filepos: 019e8
timestamp: ::45:682, filepos: 01a28
timestamp: ::49:102, filepos: 01a40
timestamp: ::51:271, filepos: 01a50
timestamp: ::54:440, filepos: 01a78
timestamp: ::56:276, filepos: 01a90
timestamp: ::59:570, filepos: 01ab8
timestamp: ::03:116, filepos: 01af8
timestamp: ::04:826, filepos: 01b20
timestamp: ::07:954, filepos: 01b38
timestamp: ::10:415, filepos: 01b58
timestamp: ::18:339, filepos: 01b80
timestamp: ::23:928, filepos: 01b90
timestamp: ::26:931, filepos: 01ba8
timestamp: ::30:143, filepos: 01bc8
timestamp: ::33:146, filepos: 01c08
timestamp: ::35:231, filepos: 01c30
timestamp: ::37:025, filepos: 01c50
timestamp: ::40:862, filepos: 01c88
timestamp: ::43:281, filepos: 01ca8
timestamp: ::46:743, filepos: 01cd0
timestamp: ::49:412, filepos: 01cf8
timestamp: ::52:165, filepos: 01d28
timestamp: ::54:876, filepos: 01d50
timestamp: ::58:212, filepos: 01d80
timestamp: :::2, filepos: 01da8
timestamp: ::04:093, filepos: 01dc8
timestamp: ::07:889, filepos: 01df0
timestamp: ::10:266, filepos: 01e08
timestamp: ::24:155, filepos: 01e30
timestamp: ::26:199, filepos: 01e38
timestamp: ::28:451, filepos: 01e50
timestamp: ::30:828, filepos: 01e78
timestamp: ::33:873, filepos: 01ea0
timestamp: ::36:834, filepos: 01ed0
timestamp: ::41:422, filepos: 01f
timestamp: ::43:841, filepos: 01f18
timestamp: ::45:885, filepos: 01f38
timestamp: ::48:596, filepos: 01f60
timestamp: ::53:101, filepos: 01f80
timestamp: ::55:853, filepos: 01fb0
timestamp: ::57:939, filepos: 01fc0
timestamp: ::58:022, filepos: 01fd0
timestamp: ::16:958, filepos: 01fe0
timestamp: ::20:545, filepos: 01ff8
timestamp: ::23:089, filepos: 02018
timestamp: ::25:091, filepos: 02028
timestamp: ::27:927, filepos: 02040
timestamp: ::31:681, filepos: 02068
timestamp: ::36:519, filepos: 02088
timestamp: ::40:773, filepos: 020a0
timestamp: ::45:445, filepos: 020b0
timestamp: ::48:614, filepos: 020d0
timestamp: ::52:618, filepos: 020d8
timestamp: ::56:164, filepos: 020f8
timestamp: :::918, filepos: 02110
timestamp: ::04:338, filepos: 02128
timestamp: ::07:592, filepos: 02138
timestamp: ::11:137, filepos: 02148
timestamp: ::15:057, filepos: 020
timestamp: ::18:561, filepos: 02180
timestamp: ::22:482, filepos: 02198
timestamp: ::25:943, filepos: 021b0
timestamp: ::29:489, filepos: 021c0
timestamp: ::36:2, filepos: 021d8
timestamp: ::39:081, filepos: 02208
timestamp: ::44:545, filepos: 02230
timestamp: ::50:259, filepos: 02250
timestamp: ::54:222, filepos: 02278
timestamp: ::58:851, filepos: 022a8
timestamp: ::07:068, filepos: 022b8
timestamp: ::09:070, filepos: 022c8
timestamp: ::12:782, filepos: 022d0
timestamp: ::14:325, filepos: 022e0
timestamp: :::787, filepos: 023
timestamp: ::24:627, filepos: 02308
timestamp: ::29:131, filepos: 02320
timestamp: ::31:259, filepos: 02330
timestamp: ::34:387, filepos: 02348
timestamp: ::43:312, filepos: 02358
timestamp: ::01:497, filepos: 02368
timestamp: ::09:5, filepos: 02378
timestamp: ::11:215, filepos: 02388
timestamp: ::16:804, filepos: 02398
timestamp: ::19:640, filepos: 023a0
timestamp: ::21:767, filepos: 023c8
timestamp: ::25:563, filepos: 023e8
timestamp: ::27:857, filepos: 02408
timestamp: ::31:777, filepos: 02438
timestamp: ::36:365, filepos: 02470
timestamp: ::38:784, filepos: 02498
timestamp: ::40:870, filepos: 024b0
timestamp: ::43:331, filepos: 024d0
timestamp: ::45:750, filepos: 024d8
timestamp: ::50:463, filepos: 024f0
timestamp: ::54:091, filepos: 024f8
timestamp: ::56:927, filepos: 025
timestamp: ::59:805, filepos: 02548
timestamp: ::01:807, filepos: 02560
timestamp: ::03:976, filepos: 02588
timestamp: ::06:771, filepos: 025c0
timestamp: ::27:833, filepos: 025e8
timestamp: ::29:9, filepos: 02610
timestamp: ::32:588, filepos: 02638
timestamp: ::34:674, filepos: 02658
timestamp: ::39:428, filepos: 02680
timestamp: ::02:1, filepos: 02690
timestamp: ::07:832, filepos: 026a0
timestamp: ::10:167, filepos: 026a8
timestamp: ::15:881, filepos: 026b0
timestamp: ::23:055, filepos: 026c8
timestamp: ::26:183, filepos: 026d0
timestamp: ::28:477, filepos: 026f8
timestamp: ::30:855, filepos: 02718
timestamp: ::35:693, filepos: 02748
timestamp: ::38:821, filepos: 02760
timestamp: ::41:240, filepos: 02780
timestamp: ::43:534, filepos: 027a0
timestamp: ::46:537, filepos: 027c0
timestamp: ::48:956, filepos: 027d8
timestamp: ::52:376, filepos: 027f8
timestamp: ::55:463, filepos: 028
timestamp: ::58:883, filepos: 02858
timestamp: ::02:595, filepos: 02890
timestamp: ::04:805, filepos: 028b0
timestamp: ::07:016, filepos: 028d8
timestamp: ::09:101, filepos: 029
timestamp: ::11:312, filepos: 02918
timestamp: ::14:023, filepos: 02950
timestamp: ::16:275, filepos: 02968
timestamp: :::280, filepos: 02988
timestamp: ::27:828, filepos: 029a8
timestamp: ::30:331, filepos: 029d0
timestamp: ::44:011, filepos: 029e8
timestamp: ::52:478, filepos: 029f8
timestamp: ::55:731, filepos: 02a10
timestamp: ::58:317, filepos: 02a20
timestamp: ::02:8, filepos: 02a38
timestamp: ::04:824, filepos: 02a50
timestamp: ::11:664, filepos: 02a68
timestamp: ::26:136, filepos: 02a78
timestamp: ::51:745, filepos: 02a90
timestamp: ::04:8, filepos: 02aa0
timestamp: ::20:649, filepos: 02ab0
timestamp: ::24:403, filepos: 02ac0
timestamp: ::27:406, filepos: 02ad0
timestamp: ::35:581, filepos: 02ae0
timestamp: ::38:208, filepos: 02ae8
timestamp: ::45:299, filepos: 02af8
timestamp: ::49:845, filepos: 02b
timestamp: ::04:276, filepos: 02b08
timestamp: ::15:996, filepos: 02b20
timestamp: ::18:082, filepos: 02b28
timestamp: ::23:337, filepos: 02b60
timestamp: ::27:591, filepos: 02b70
timestamp: ::30:344, filepos: 02b80
timestamp: ::52:658, filepos: 02b90
timestamp: ::56:996, filepos: 02ba0
timestamp: :::249, filepos: 02bb0
timestamp: ::03:627, filepos: 02bb8
timestamp: ::20:144, filepos: 02bd0
timestamp: ::26:984, filepos: 02be0
timestamp: ::43:167, filepos: 02bf0
timestamp: ::45:127, filepos: 02c
timestamp: ::59:308, filepos: 02c18
timestamp: ::03:145, filepos: 02c30
timestamp: ::05:272, filepos: 02c48
timestamp: ::12:988, filepos: 02c58
timestamp: ::15:407, filepos: 02c78
timestamp: ::18:410, filepos: 02ca0
timestamp: ::20:621, filepos: 02cb8
timestamp: ::23:290, filepos: 02cd8
timestamp: :::210, filepos: 02d
timestamp: ::34:134, filepos: 02d28
timestamp: ::38:013, filepos: 02d48
timestamp: ::39:848, filepos: 02d68
timestamp: ::51:318, filepos: 02d88
timestamp: ::54:321, filepos: 02db0
timestamp: ::59:201, filepos: 02dc0
timestamp: ::03:872, filepos: 02dd8
timestamp: ::06:875, filepos: 02e
timestamp: ::08:919, filepos: 02e20
timestamp: ::11:380, filepos: 02e40
timestamp: ::15:342, filepos: 02e88
timestamp: ::19:221, filepos: 02eb0
timestamp: ::21:515, filepos: 02ec8
timestamp: ::26:687, filepos: 02ee8
timestamp: ::31:733, filepos: 02f10
timestamp: ::36:238, filepos: 02f28
timestamp: ::39:658, filepos: 02f58
timestamp: ::44:288, filepos: 02f70
timestamp: ::46:373, filepos: 02f90
timestamp: ::51:545, filepos: 02fc0
timestamp: ::58:093, filepos: 02fd0
timestamp: ::59:803, filepos: 02fd8
timestamp: ::01:555, filepos: 02ff0
timestamp: ::03:682, filepos: 03018
timestamp: ::06:143, filepos: 03040
timestamp: ::08:937, filepos: 03058
timestamp: ::11:398, filepos: 03080
timestamp: ::15:736, filepos: 03090
timestamp: ::19:531, filepos: 030a8
timestamp: ::21:575, filepos: 030b8
timestamp: ::25:996, filepos: 030e0
timestamp: ::30:417, filepos: 030f8
timestamp: ::34:963, filepos: 03110
timestamp: ::38:217, filepos: 031
timestamp: ::40:886, filepos: 03138
timestamp: ::44:932, filepos: 03158
timestamp: ::46:934, filepos: 03168
timestamp: ::48:936, filepos: 03180
timestamp: ::52:522, filepos: 031a8
timestamp: ::58:278, filepos: 031c8
timestamp: ::01:865, filepos: 031e0
timestamp: ::04:743, filepos: 031f0
timestamp: ::18:6, filepos: 032
timestamp: ::27:432, filepos: 03210
timestamp: ::30:394, filepos: 03220
timestamp: ::34:189, filepos: 03250
timestamp: ::38:694, filepos: 030
timestamp: ::41:280, filepos: 032a8
timestamp: ::43:991, filepos: 032b0
timestamp: ::48:996, filepos: 032d8
timestamp: ::53:5, filepos: 032f0
timestamp: ::57:838, filepos: 03338
timestamp: :::882, filepos: 03368
timestamp: ::06:013, filepos: 03398
timestamp: ::09:641, filepos: 033d0
timestamp: ::11:351, filepos: 033d8
timestamp: ::15:605, filepos: 03410
timestamp: ::17:607, filepos: 03428
timestamp: ::21:236, filepos: 03438
timestamp: ::23:905, filepos: 03468
timestamp: ::25:782, filepos: 03488
timestamp: ::28:243, filepos: 034b0
timestamp: ::29:995, filepos: 034c8
timestamp: ::33:040, filepos: 035
timestamp: ::35:709, filepos: 03520
timestamp: ::37:544, filepos: 035
timestamp: ::43:383, filepos: 03568
timestamp: ::46:553, filepos: 03570
timestamp: ::48:597, filepos: 03588
timestamp: ::55:062, filepos: 03598
timestamp: ::57:147, filepos: 035b8
timestamp: ::59:316, filepos: 035e0
timestamp: ::01:401, filepos: 03608
timestamp: ::05:447, filepos: 03640
timestamp: ::09:868, filepos: 03660
timestamp: ::14:956, filepos: 03688
timestamp: ::17:959, filepos: 03698
timestamp: ::20:253, filepos: 036a8
timestamp: ::28:053, filepos: 036b8
timestamp: :::014, filepos: 036d0
timestamp: ::37:646, filepos: 036e8
timestamp: ::43:193, filepos: 036f8
timestamp: ::47:864, filepos: 03708
timestamp: ::51:993, filepos: 03738
timestamp: ::55:872, filepos: 03758
timestamp: ::58:291, filepos: 03770
timestamp: ::01:128, filepos: 03788
timestamp: ::05:799, filepos: 037b8
timestamp: ::08:885, filepos: 037d8
timestamp: ::13:223, filepos: 038
timestamp: ::17:519, filepos: 03820
timestamp: ::20:647, filepos: 03838
timestamp: ::27:654, filepos: 03850
timestamp: :::909, filepos: 03860
timestamp: ::36:913, filepos: 03870
timestamp: ::39:374, filepos: 03878
timestamp: ::43:503, filepos: 03898
timestamp: ::47:090, filepos: 038b8
timestamp: ::57:517, filepos: 038c8
timestamp: ::12:240, filepos: 038d8
timestamp: ::15:702, filepos: 038f8
timestamp: ::22:083, filepos: 039
timestamp: ::27:5, filepos: 03910
timestamp: ::29:716, filepos: 03928
timestamp: ::32:052, filepos: 03940
timestamp: ::34:846, filepos: 03950
timestamp: ::40:477, filepos: 03958
timestamp: ::43:980, filepos: 03968
timestamp: ::46:441, filepos: 03978
timestamp: ::55:534, filepos: 03988
timestamp: ::04:501, filepos: 03990
timestamp: ::08:255, filepos: 03998
timestamp: ::13:218, filepos: 039a0
timestamp: ::17:264, filepos: 039b0
timestamp: ::19:933, filepos: 039b8
timestamp: ::22:477, filepos: 039e0
timestamp: ::26:523, filepos: 03a
timestamp: ::29:985, filepos: 03a08
timestamp: ::31:945, filepos: 03a18
timestamp: ::35:115, filepos: 03a30
timestamp: ::41:705, filepos: 03a48
timestamp: ::43:748, filepos: 03a58
timestamp: ::47:919, filepos: 03a70
timestamp: ::53:508, filepos: 03a80
timestamp: ::53:592, filepos: 03ab0
timestamp: ::56:4, filepos: 03ae0
timestamp: ::59:139, filepos: 03b10
timestamp: ::03:560, filepos: 03b48
timestamp: ::07:522, filepos: 03b80
timestamp: ::10:233, filepos: 03ba0
timestamp: ::13:486, filepos: 03bd0
timestamp: ::17:949, filepos: 03c10
timestamp: ::20:702, filepos: 03c30
timestamp: ::22:704, filepos: 03c50
timestamp: ::24:998, filepos: 03c70
timestamp: ::27:542, filepos: 03c88
timestamp: ::32:422, filepos: 03cb8
timestamp: :::967, filepos: 03cd0
timestamp: ::44:809, filepos: 03cf0
timestamp: ::49:689, filepos: 03cf8
timestamp: ::51:858, filepos: 03d08
timestamp: ::54:694, filepos: 03d28
timestamp: ::57:572, filepos: 03d40
timestamp: ::59:658, filepos: 03d58
timestamp: ::02:661, filepos: 03d60
timestamp: ::06:539, filepos: 03d88
timestamp: ::09:209, filepos: 03db0
timestamp: ::12:3, filepos: 03db8
timestamp: ::14:714, filepos: 03dd0
timestamp: ::19:344, filepos: 03e
timestamp: ::25:225, filepos: 03e20
timestamp: ::29:062, filepos: 03e30
timestamp: ::33:650, filepos: 03e68
timestamp: :::528, filepos: 03e80
timestamp: ::38:530, filepos: 03e90
timestamp: ::43:868, filepos: 03ec8
timestamp: ::55:213, filepos: 03ee8
timestamp: ::01:010, filepos: 03ef8
timestamp: ::05:390, filepos: 03f20
timestamp: ::08:435, filepos: 03f30
timestamp: ::10:311, filepos: 03f38
timestamp: ::13:982, filepos: 03f50
timestamp: ::17:944, filepos: 03f78
timestamp: ::22:699, filepos: 03fa0
timestamp: ::16:920, filepos: 03fb8
timestamp: ::19:047, filepos: 03fe0
timestamp: ::21:132, filepos: 04010
timestamp: ::23:259, filepos: 04028
timestamp: ::28:9, filepos: 04040
timestamp: ::31:059, filepos: 04078
timestamp: ::35:063, filepos: 040a0
timestamp: ::37:941, filepos: 040b8
timestamp: ::39:943, filepos: 040c8
timestamp: ::42:278, filepos: 040f0
timestamp: ::44:781, filepos: 04120
timestamp: ::47:992, filepos: 04140
timestamp: ::52:288, filepos: 04178
timestamp: ::54:290, filepos: 04188
timestamp: ::56:084, filepos: 041a0
timestamp: ::57:919, filepos: 041b8
timestamp: ::01:130, filepos: 041e8
timestamp: ::03:925, filepos: 04208
timestamp: ::06:052, filepos: 04220
timestamp: ::07:762, filepos: 04230
timestamp: ::09:889, filepos: 04248
timestamp: ::13:059, filepos: 04268
timestamp: ::16:271, filepos: 04280
timestamp: ::18:481, filepos: 04290
timestamp: ::21:818, filepos: 042b8
timestamp: ::24:153, filepos: 042e8
timestamp: ::26:906, filepos: 04308
timestamp: ::28:825, filepos: 04328
timestamp: ::30:952, filepos: 04350
timestamp: ::34:247, filepos: 04360
timestamp: ::36:916, filepos: 04380
timestamp: :::127, filepos: 043a0
timestamp: ::41:588, filepos: 043c8
timestamp: ::45:8, filepos: 043e0
timestamp: ::49:012, filepos: 044
timestamp: ::51:681, filepos: 04428
timestamp: ::55:768, filepos: 04458
timestamp: ::57:770, filepos: 04470
timestamp: ::01:399, filepos: 04478
timestamp: ::03:318, filepos: 04488
timestamp: ::07:113, filepos: 04498
timestamp: ::09:157, filepos: 044b0
timestamp: ::11:784, filepos: 044d0
timestamp: ::15:788, filepos: 04518
timestamp: ::17:373, filepos: 04528
timestamp: ::19:876, filepos: 04560
timestamp: ::21:878, filepos: 04570
timestamp: ::25:298, filepos: 045b8
timestamp: ::27:3, filepos: 045d0
timestamp: ::31:512, filepos: 04608
timestamp: ::34:682, filepos: 04618
timestamp: ::37:518, filepos: 04630
timestamp: ::39:729, filepos: 04650
timestamp: ::41:272, filepos: 04668
timestamp: ::43:608, filepos: 046a0
timestamp: ::47:278, filepos: 046b8
timestamp: ::50:365, filepos: 046d8
timestamp: ::53:9, filepos: 046f8
timestamp: ::55:578, filepos: 04710
timestamp: ::57:580, filepos: 04720
timestamp: :::166, filepos: 04740
timestamp: ::03:753, filepos: 04758
timestamp: ::07:173, filepos: 04778
timestamp: ::09:926, filepos: 047a0
timestamp: ::13:179, filepos: 047c8
timestamp: ::15:181, filepos: 047d8
timestamp: ::18:267, filepos: 048
timestamp: ::23:064, filepos: 04820
timestamp: ::27:860, filepos: 04838
timestamp: ::31:739, filepos: 04870
timestamp: ::33:950, filepos: 04898
timestamp: ::37:704, filepos: 048c0
timestamp: :::207, filepos: 048f0
timestamp: ::47:714, filepos: 04928
timestamp: ::50:925, filepos: 04948
timestamp: ::54:387, filepos: 04958
timestamp: ::58:099, filepos: 04968
timestamp: ::01:728, filepos: 04980
timestamp: ::05:565, filepos: 049a0
timestamp: ::09:235, filepos: 049b8
timestamp: ::12:780, filepos: 049d0
timestamp: ::16:159, filepos: 049e0
timestamp: ::19:746, filepos: 049f8
timestamp: ::22:373, filepos: 04a18
timestamp: ::26:377, filepos: 04a48
timestamp: ::29:2, filepos: 04a58
timestamp: ::32:884, filepos: 04a70
timestamp: ::37:180, filepos: 04aa0
timestamp: ::40:099, filepos: 04ac8
timestamp: ::43:436, filepos: 04ae0
timestamp: ::46:147, filepos: 04af8
timestamp: ::47:982, filepos: 04b18
timestamp: ::50:109, filepos: 04b28
timestamp: ::52:403, filepos: 04b48
timestamp: ::55:490, filepos: 04b70
timestamp: ::58:534, filepos: 04b98
timestamp: ::02:205, filepos: 04bc8
timestamp: ::06:375, filepos: 04bf0
timestamp: ::09:3, filepos: 04c10
timestamp: ::11:881, filepos: 04c30
timestamp: ::14:467, filepos: 04c58
timestamp: ::17:470, filepos: 04c80
timestamp: ::19:472, filepos: 04c98
timestamp: ::22:517, filepos: 04cb0
timestamp: ::27:230, filepos: 04cc8
timestamp: ::31:484, filepos: 04cf0
timestamp: ::33:569, filepos: 04d10
timestamp: ::36:697, filepos: 04d30
timestamp: ::38:991, filepos: 04d50
timestamp: ::41:661, filepos: 04d78
timestamp: :::913, filepos: 04d88
timestamp: ::47:208, filepos: 04da0
timestamp: ::51:629, filepos: 04de0
timestamp: ::54:382, filepos: 04e08
timestamp: ::56:801, filepos: 04e28
timestamp: ::02:223, filepos: 04e40
timestamp: ::04:684, filepos: 04e58
timestamp: ::07:061, filepos: 04e78
timestamp: ::09:147, filepos: 04e98
timestamp: ::12:358, filepos: 04eb8
timestamp: ::16:279, filepos: 04ee0
timestamp: ::21:159, filepos: 04f10
timestamp: ::25:121, filepos: 04f30
timestamp: ::25:204, filepos: 04f60
timestamp: ::28:499, filepos: 04f90
timestamp: ::33:629, filepos: 04fc0
timestamp: ::37:592, filepos: 04fd8
timestamp: ::39:635, filepos: 04ff8
timestamp: :::557, filepos: 058
timestamp: ::46:726, filepos: 05018
timestamp: ::49:645, filepos: 05030
timestamp: ::53:065, filepos: 05068
timestamp: ::56:319, filepos: 05080
timestamp: ::58:821, filepos: 050a0
timestamp: ::01:741, filepos: 050c8
timestamp: ::04:243, filepos: 050f0
timestamp: ::07:413, filepos: 051
timestamp: ::13:252, filepos: 05130
timestamp: ::16:088, filepos: 05140
timestamp: ::19:550, filepos: 05168
timestamp: ::24:013, filepos: 051a0
timestamp: ::27:934, filepos: 051d8
timestamp: ::31:520, filepos: 051f0
timestamp: ::37:026, filepos: 05218
timestamp: ::42:448, filepos: 05230
timestamp: ::47:912, filepos: 05260
timestamp: ::49:914, filepos: 05270
timestamp: ::52:583, filepos: 05290
timestamp: ::56:420, filepos: 052c0
timestamp: ::05:596, filepos: 052d0
timestamp: ::09:517, filepos: 052e0
timestamp: ::12:186, filepos: 05308
timestamp: ::16:440, filepos: 05340
timestamp: ::20:736, filepos: 05368
timestamp: ::22:989, filepos: 05370
timestamp: ::26:075, filepos: 05388
timestamp: ::29:870, filepos: 053a0
timestamp: ::34:458, filepos: 053a8
timestamp: ::38:4, filepos: 053b0
timestamp: ::41:215, filepos: 053c8
timestamp: ::44:510, filepos: 053d8
timestamp: ::47:3, filepos: 053e8
timestamp: ::50:016, filepos: 05410
timestamp: ::55:271, filepos: 05440
timestamp: ::58:316, filepos: 05470
timestamp: ::01:652, filepos: 05498
timestamp: ::03:571, filepos: 054c0
timestamp: ::07:158, filepos: 054e0
timestamp: ::10:745, filepos: 054f8
timestamp: ::16:709, filepos: 055
timestamp: ::20:421, filepos: 05538
timestamp: ::24:550, filepos: 05568
timestamp: ::28:596, filepos: 05588
timestamp: ::31:932, filepos: 055b0
timestamp: ::37:146, filepos: 055e0
timestamp: ::42:818, filepos: 05608
timestamp: ::46:655, filepos: 05620
timestamp: ::48:949, filepos: 05628
timestamp: ::09:804, filepos: 05638
timestamp: ::12:681, filepos: 056
timestamp: ::17:269, filepos: 05678
timestamp: ::21:399, filepos: 05698
timestamp: ::25:903, filepos: 056c0
timestamp: ::30:908, filepos: 056e8
timestamp: ::36:288, filepos: 05710
timestamp: ::40:751, filepos: 05730
timestamp: ::43:712, filepos: 05750
timestamp: ::14:952, filepos: 05778
timestamp: ::57:870, filepos: 05790
timestamp: ::37:785, filepos: 057a0
timestamp: ::40:704, filepos: 057a8
timestamp: ::48:4, filepos: 057b8
timestamp: ::51:257, filepos: 057c0
timestamp: ::56:011, filepos: 057f8
timestamp: ::58:722, filepos: 05810
timestamp: :::766, filepos: 05828
timestamp: ::04:436, filepos: 05840
timestamp: ::10:693, filepos: 05858
timestamp: ::18:993, filepos: 05868
timestamp: ::24:832, filepos: 05880
timestamp: ::26:667, filepos: 05890
timestamp: ::30:212, filepos: 058c0
timestamp: ::32:339, filepos: 058d0
timestamp: ::34:550, filepos: 058f8
timestamp: ::37:303, filepos: 05928
timestamp: ::39:763, filepos: 05950
timestamp: ::41:932, filepos: 05970
timestamp: ::44:310, filepos: 059a0
timestamp: ::45:978, filepos: 059b8
timestamp: ::48:772, filepos: 059d0
timestamp: :::191, filepos: 059e0
timestamp: ::53:444, filepos: 05a
timestamp: ::55:446, filepos: 05a18
timestamp: ::58:616, filepos: 05a30
timestamp: ::02:661, filepos: 05a48
timestamp: ::05:456, filepos: 05a58
timestamp: ::08:417, filepos: 05a70
timestamp: ::15:549, filepos: 05a88
timestamp: ::20:971, filepos: 05aa0
timestamp: ::28:854, filepos: 05ab0
timestamp: ::32:107, filepos: 05ab8
timestamp: ::35:7, filepos: 05ad0
timestamp: ::37:9, filepos: 05ad8
timestamp: ::42:326, filepos: 05af8
timestamp: ::53:462, filepos: 05b18
timestamp: ::56:256, filepos: 05b40
timestamp: ::58:759, filepos: 05b48
timestamp: ::02:638, filepos: 05b68
timestamp: ::05:140, filepos: 05b78
timestamp: ::25:661, filepos: 05b90
timestamp: ::37:673, filepos: 05b98
timestamp: ::48:058, filepos: 05ba8
timestamp: ::51:729, filepos: 05bc0
timestamp: ::54:440, filepos: 05bd8
timestamp: ::58:694, filepos: 05c10
timestamp: ::05:284, filepos: 05c30
timestamp: ::16:670, filepos: 05c40
timestamp: ::33:020, filepos: 05c58
timestamp: ::41:403, filepos: 05c60
timestamp: ::43:739, filepos: 05c80
timestamp: ::45:908, filepos: 05c90
timestamp: ::50:788, filepos: 05cb0
timestamp: ::53:123, filepos: 05cc8
timestamp: ::03:592, filepos: 05ce8
timestamp: ::12:059, filepos: 05cf8
timestamp: ::15:896, filepos: 05d08
timestamp: ::24:988, filepos: 05d20
timestamp: ::30:202, filepos: 05d30
timestamp: ::32:663, filepos: 05d40
timestamp: ::34:540, filepos: 05d48
timestamp: ::41:630, filepos: 05d58
timestamp: ::44:466, filepos: 05d70
timestamp: ::49:721, filepos: 05d78
timestamp: ::54:017, filepos: 05d88
timestamp: ::57:604, filepos: 05da0
timestamp: :::649, filepos: 05da8
timestamp: ::05:904, filepos: 05db8
timestamp: ::12:035, filepos: 05dc8
timestamp: ::15:789, filepos: 05dd0
timestamp: ::19:793, filepos: 05df0
timestamp: ::23:505, filepos: 05e08
timestamp: ::29:136, filepos: 05e18
timestamp: ::43:692, filepos: 05e28
timestamp: ::51:408, filepos: 05e38
timestamp: ::54:703, filepos: 05e60
timestamp: ::57:998, filepos: 05e78
timestamp: ::30:697, filepos: 05e88
timestamp: ::40:666, filepos: 05e98
timestamp: ::09:945, filepos: 05ea8
timestamp: ::15:617, filepos: 05eb8
timestamp: ::22:040, filepos: 05ed0
timestamp: ::44:604, filepos: 05ee0
timestamp: ::59:161, filepos: 05ef8
timestamp: ::26:438, filepos: 05f08
timestamp: ::28:648, filepos: 05f18
timestamp: ::30:442, filepos: 05f28
timestamp: ::34:279, filepos: 05f58
timestamp: ::38:325, filepos: 05f70
timestamp: ::47:250, filepos: 05fa0
timestamp: ::58:553, filepos: 05fb8
timestamp: ::03:243, filepos: 0005fd000
timestamp: ::08:665, filepos: 0005fe000
timestamp: ::10:667, filepos: 0005ff800
timestamp: ::12:586, filepos: 0006000
timestamp: ::15:630, filepos: 000603800
timestamp: ::18:842, filepos: 000606800
timestamp: ::21:845, filepos: 000609000
timestamp: ::24:222, filepos: 00060b000
timestamp: ::26:349, filepos: 00060c800
timestamp: ::28:685, filepos: 00060e800
timestamp: ::31:938, filepos: 000610000
timestamp: ::33:940, filepos: 000611800
timestamp: ::37:277, filepos: 000613800
timestamp: ::40:280, filepos: 000615800
timestamp: ::43:658, filepos: 000616000
timestamp: ::47:329, filepos: 000619000
timestamp: ::51:208, filepos: 00061b800
timestamp: ::54:211, filepos: 00061d800
timestamp: ::56:213, filepos: 00061f000
timestamp: ::05:3, filepos: 000620000
timestamp: ::06:723, filepos: 000622000
timestamp: ::09:059, filepos: 000624000
timestamp: ::13:396, filepos: 000626000
timestamp: ::16:149, filepos: 000627800
timestamp: ::18:235, filepos: 000628800
timestamp: ::20:320, filepos: 000629800
timestamp: ::24:407, filepos: 00062b800
timestamp: ::28:495, filepos: 00062d000
timestamp: ::32:123, filepos: 00062f800
timestamp: ::35:126, filepos: 000631000
timestamp: ::38:129, filepos: 000633000
timestamp: ::42:050, filepos: 000635800
timestamp: ::44:052, filepos: 000636800
timestamp: ::47:597, filepos: 000638800
timestamp: ::50:684, filepos: 00063b000
timestamp: ::53:687, filepos: 00063d800
timestamp: ::59:317, filepos: 000641000
timestamp: ::06:908, filepos: 000642000
timestamp: ::09:160, filepos: 000644000
timestamp: ::13:623, filepos: 000647000
timestamp: ::16:668, filepos: 000647800
timestamp: ::22:924, filepos: 000649800
timestamp: ::25:135, filepos: 00064a000
timestamp: ::28:138, filepos: 00064d000
timestamp: ::32:058, filepos: 00064e800
timestamp: ::39:899, filepos: 000652800
timestamp: ::46:197, filepos: 000654000
timestamp: ::48:700, filepos: 000656800
timestamp: ::51:369, filepos: 000657800
timestamp: ::56:333, filepos: 00065a800
timestamp: ::58:209, filepos: 00065c000
timestamp: :::296, filepos: 00065e000
timestamp: ::05:675, filepos: 00065f800
timestamp: ::07:510, filepos: 000660000
timestamp: ::09:721, filepos: 000661800
timestamp: ::13:099, filepos: 000663800
timestamp: ::19:814, filepos: 000666000
timestamp: ::22:025, filepos: 000667800
timestamp: ::24:444, filepos: 000668800
timestamp: ::27:447, filepos: 00066a000
timestamp: ::34:621, filepos: 00066c800
timestamp: ::36:623, filepos: 00066e800
timestamp: ::39:292, filepos: 000670000
timestamp: ::43:630, filepos: 000673800
timestamp: ::46:424, filepos: 000675800
timestamp: ::54:140, filepos: 000678000
timestamp: ::56:518, filepos: 000678800
timestamp: ::59:646, filepos: 00067c000
timestamp: ::03:066, filepos: 00067e000
timestamp: :::735, filepos: 000680000
timestamp: ::09:572, filepos: 000682800
timestamp: ::12:283, filepos: 000684000
timestamp: ::15:703, filepos: 000688000
timestamp: ::19:290, filepos: 00068b800
timestamp: ::21:668, filepos: 00068d800
timestamp: ::24:671, filepos: 000691000
timestamp: ::27:173, filepos: 000694000
timestamp: ::29:759, filepos: 000696000
timestamp: ::31:594, filepos: 000697000
timestamp: ::42:063, filepos: 00069b000
timestamp: ::44:149, filepos: 00069e000
timestamp: ::47:318, filepos: 0006a0000
timestamp: ::50:238, filepos: 0006a1800
timestamp: ::53:366, filepos: 0006a4800
timestamp: ::54:909, filepos: 0006a5800
timestamp: ::58:746, filepos: 0006a8000
timestamp: ::02:208, filepos: 00ab000
timestamp: ::05:712, filepos: 00ad000
timestamp: ::07:547, filepos: 00af800
timestamp: ::11:050, filepos: 00b1800
timestamp: ::13:803, filepos: 00b3800
timestamp: ::16:639, filepos: 00b5000
timestamp: ::20:310, filepos: 00b6800
timestamp: ::23:521, filepos: 00b8000
timestamp: ::26:733, filepos: 00ba000
timestamp: ::30:195, filepos: 00bb800
timestamp: ::34:741, filepos: 00bc800
timestamp: ::38:411, filepos: 00bd800
timestamp: ::45:502, filepos: 00bf000
timestamp: ::47:462, filepos: 00c0000
timestamp: ::49:464, filepos: 00c1800
timestamp: ::53:760, filepos: 00c5800
timestamp: ::00:308, filepos: 0006c7000
timestamp: ::23:498, filepos: 0006c8000
timestamp: ::28:878, filepos: 0006c9000
timestamp: ::32:131, filepos: 0006cc800
timestamp: ::49:023, filepos: 0006cf800
timestamp: ::51:568, filepos: 0006d0800
timestamp: ::54:237, filepos: 0006d2800
timestamp: ::57:782, filepos: 0006d4000
timestamp: ::00:827, filepos: 0006d5800
timestamp: ::06:332, filepos: 0006d6800
timestamp: ::20:221, filepos: 0006d7800
timestamp: ::23:182, filepos: 0006d8000
timestamp: ::29:063, filepos: 0006d9800
timestamp: ::33:443, filepos: 0006da800
timestamp: ::39:907, filepos: 0006dc800
timestamp: ::48:291, filepos: 0006de000
timestamp: ::50:418, filepos: 0006df000
timestamp: ::54:130, filepos: 0006e1000
timestamp: ::58:384, filepos: 0006e4000
timestamp: ::00:845, filepos: 0006e6000
timestamp: ::04:057, filepos: 0006e7000
timestamp: :::145, filepos: 0006e9800
timestamp: ::13:941, filepos: 0006eb000
timestamp: ::23:117, filepos: 0006ed000
timestamp: ::30:041, filepos: 0006ef000
timestamp: ::35:338, filepos: 0006f2000
timestamp: ::40:510, filepos: 0006f3800
timestamp: ::44:055, filepos: 0006f7000
timestamp: ::47:8, filepos: 0006f9000
timestamp: ::51:062, filepos: 0006fa800
timestamp: ::53:773, filepos: 0006fb800
timestamp: ::56:567, filepos: 0006fe800
timestamp: ::59:570, filepos: 0007000
timestamp: ::18:256, filepos: 000703800
timestamp: ::21:426, filepos: 000706000
timestamp: ::48:911, filepos: 000707000
timestamp: ::53:666, filepos: 000709800
timestamp: ::56:669, filepos: 00070c000
timestamp: ::58:880, filepos: 00070d000
timestamp: :::674, filepos: 00070e000
timestamp: ::05:678, filepos: 000710000
timestamp: ::09:557, filepos: 000712800
timestamp: ::13:186, filepos: 000715000
timestamp: ::15:772, filepos: 000717000
timestamp: ::24:781, filepos: 000718800
timestamp: ::27:6, filepos: 00071a000
timestamp: ::29:8, filepos: 00071b800
timestamp: ::30:828, filepos: 00071c800
timestamp: ::36:125, filepos: 000720800
timestamp: ::38:127, filepos: 000722800
timestamp: ::42:924, filepos: 000725000
timestamp: ::47:1, filepos: 000728000
timestamp: ::50:181, filepos: 00072a000
timestamp: ::53:893, filepos: 00072c000
timestamp: ::55:436, filepos: 00072c800
timestamp: ::58:648, filepos: 00072e000
timestamp: ::02:485, filepos: 000730000
timestamp: ::04:904, filepos: 000731800
timestamp: ::09:075, filepos: 000733800
timestamp: ::16:582, filepos: 000735800
timestamp: ::18:5, filepos: 000736000
timestamp: ::20:837, filepos: 000737800
timestamp: ::26:008, filepos: 000739800
timestamp: ::42:358, filepos: 00073b000
timestamp: ::46:821, filepos: 00073e800
timestamp: ::50:366, filepos: 000742800
timestamp: ::53:160, filepos: 000744000
timestamp: ::56:247, filepos: 000746000
timestamp: ::00:877, filepos: 000747800
timestamp: ::04:171, filepos: 00074a000
timestamp: ::06:549, filepos: 00074b000
timestamp: ::09:176, filepos: 00074c800
timestamp: ::25:192, filepos: 00074d800
timestamp: ::27:987, filepos: 00074f000
timestamp: ::30:990, filepos: 000750800
timestamp: ::34:076, filepos: 000752000
timestamp: ::36:579, filepos: 000753000
timestamp: ::39:248, filepos: 000755000
timestamp: ::48:716, filepos: 000758000
timestamp: ::53:387, filepos: 00075b000
timestamp: ::13:908, filepos: 00075d000
timestamp: ::16:494, filepos: 00075d800
timestamp: ::18:537, filepos: 00075f000
timestamp: ::23:000, filepos: 000761800
timestamp: ::25:461, filepos: 000763800
timestamp: ::27:004, filepos: 000764800
timestamp: ::30:549, filepos: 000766800
timestamp: ::32:969, filepos: 000768800
timestamp: ::35:972, filepos: 00076b000
timestamp: ::38:182, filepos: 00076d800
timestamp: ::39:892, filepos: 00076f000
timestamp: ::43:521, filepos: 000772800
timestamp: ::47:817, filepos: 000776000
timestamp: ::51:487, filepos: 000779800
timestamp: ::55:241, filepos: 00077b000
timestamp: ::57:243, filepos: 00077c000
timestamp: ::59:537, filepos: 00077d000
timestamp: :::580, filepos: 00077d800
timestamp: ::04:208, filepos: 00077f000
timestamp: ::05:751, filepos: 000780800
timestamp: ::09:880, filepos: 000783800
timestamp: ::12:216, filepos: 000785800
timestamp: ::14:885, filepos: 000787000
timestamp: ::20:182, filepos: 000788800
timestamp: ::21:851, filepos: 00078a800
timestamp: ::25:354, filepos: 00078e000
timestamp: ::26:772, filepos: 00078f800
timestamp: ::29:859, filepos: 000792800
timestamp: ::32:903, filepos: 000796800
timestamp: ::34:822, filepos: 000798000
timestamp: ::37:908, filepos: 00079b000
timestamp: ::40:369, filepos: 00079e000
timestamp: ::43:247, filepos: 0007a0800
timestamp: ::45:583, filepos: 0007a2000
timestamp: ::48:961, filepos: 0007a4800
timestamp: ::50:838, filepos: 0007a6000
timestamp: ::54:050, filepos: 0007a9000
timestamp: ::56:552, filepos: 0007aa800
timestamp: ::58:471, filepos: 0007ab800
timestamp: ::00:056, filepos: 0007ac000
timestamp: ::06:312, filepos: 0007ae000
timestamp: ::08:439, filepos: 0007af800
timestamp: ::11:025, filepos: 0007b1800
timestamp: ::14:403, filepos: 0007b4000
timestamp: ::18:449, filepos: 0007b5800
timestamp: ::20:951, filepos: 0007b7000
timestamp: ::23:370, filepos: 0007b9800
timestamp: ::25:915, filepos: 0007bb000
timestamp: ::31:754, filepos: 0007bc800
timestamp: ::35:883, filepos: 0007bf000
timestamp: ::41:472, filepos: 0007c0800
timestamp: ::45:142, filepos: 0007c2800
timestamp: ::55:069, filepos: 0007c5000
timestamp: ::57:446, filepos: 0007c7800
timestamp: ::59:615, filepos: 0007c9000
timestamp: :::659, filepos: 0007cb000
timestamp: ::06:413, filepos: 0007cc800
timestamp: ::08:582, filepos: 0007ce800
timestamp: ::10:751, filepos: 0007d0000
timestamp: ::13:212, filepos: 0007d2000
timestamp: :::842, filepos: 0007d3800
timestamp: ::20:094, filepos: 0007d4800
timestamp: ::22:9, filepos: 0007d6800
timestamp: ::24:181, filepos: 0007d8000
timestamp: ::26:058, filepos: 0007db000
timestamp: ::29:186, filepos: 0007dd000
timestamp: ::31:105, filepos: 0007df800
timestamp: ::34:275, filepos: 0007e1800
timestamp: ::37:820, filepos: 0007e3800
timestamp: ::40:739, filepos: 0007e5800
timestamp: ::45:035, filepos: 0007e8800
timestamp: ::50:457, filepos: 0007e9800
timestamp: ::52:084, filepos: 0007ea800
timestamp: ::55:504, filepos: 0007ed000
timestamp: ::00:134, filepos: 0007f0000
timestamp: ::03:888, filepos: 0007f3000
timestamp: ::06:599, filepos: 0007f5000
timestamp: ::08:893, filepos: 0007f6000
timestamp: ::14:440, filepos: 0007f8800
timestamp: ::17:943, filepos: 0007fa800
timestamp: ::20:946, filepos: 0007fd000
timestamp: ::26:911, filepos: 0007fe000
timestamp: ::29:788, filepos: 000800000
timestamp: ::33:125, filepos: 000802000
timestamp: ::36:086, filepos: 000804000
timestamp: ::38:422, filepos: 000806000
timestamp: ::41:550, filepos: 000808000
timestamp: ::44:887, filepos: 00080a800
timestamp: ::47:431, filepos: 00080c000
timestamp: ::50:4, filepos: 00080d000
timestamp: ::22:925, filepos: 00080e000
timestamp: ::24:635, filepos: 00080f000
timestamp: ::28:597, filepos: 000810800
timestamp: ::32:268, filepos: 000812000
timestamp: ::34:436, filepos: 000813000
timestamp: ::37:690, filepos: 000815800
timestamp: ::44:738, filepos: 000818000
timestamp: ::51:203, filepos: 00081a800
timestamp: ::59:420, filepos: 00081c800
timestamp: ::07:594, filepos: 00081e000
timestamp: ::13:434, filepos: 00081f800
timestamp: ::17:521, filepos: 000822800
timestamp: ::21:317, filepos: 000825000
timestamp: ::28:073, filepos: 000826800
timestamp: ::31:243, filepos: 000828800
timestamp: ::34:4, filepos: 00082a000
timestamp: ::38:334, filepos: 00082d000
timestamp: ::50:179, filepos: 00082e800
timestamp: ::52:890, filepos: 00082f800
timestamp: ::56:560, filepos: 0008300
timestamp: ::58:812, filepos: 000833800
timestamp: ::02:107, filepos: 000834000
timestamp: ::04:026, filepos: 000835000
timestamp: ::08:280, filepos: 000837800
timestamp: ::10:324, filepos: 000838800
timestamp: ::12:284, filepos: 00083a800
timestamp: ::15:079, filepos: 00083c800
timestamp: ::18:248, filepos: 00083e000
timestamp: :::418, filepos: 00083f800
timestamp: ::25:4, filepos: 000841800
timestamp: ::27:758, filepos: 000842000
timestamp: ::31:887, filepos: 000844800
timestamp: ::34:431, filepos: 000845800
timestamp: ::38:519, filepos: 000849000
timestamp: ::40:270, filepos: 00084a000
timestamp: ::44:858, filepos: 00084d000
timestamp: ::48:445, filepos: 00084e800
timestamp: ::50:447, filepos: 000850800
timestamp: ::54:076, filepos: 000853000
timestamp: ::57:079, filepos: 000855800
timestamp: ::00:791, filepos: 000857000
timestamp: ::04:128, filepos: 000858800
timestamp: ::06:130, filepos: 000859800
timestamp: ::09:591, filepos: 00085c000
timestamp: ::11:844, filepos: 00085c800
timestamp: ::15:639, filepos: 000860000
timestamp: ::20:602, filepos: 000861800
timestamp: :::604, filepos: 000862800
timestamp: ::26:275, filepos: 000864000
timestamp: ::28:652, filepos: 000866000
timestamp: ::33:532, filepos: 000869000
timestamp: ::40:456, filepos: 00086a800
timestamp: ::45:127, filepos: 00086c800
timestamp: ::47:463, filepos: 00086e000
timestamp: ::49:965, filepos: 000870800
timestamp: ::53:469, filepos: 000872800
timestamp: ::00:309, filepos: 000874000
timestamp: ::03:395, filepos: 000876000
timestamp: ::07:065, filepos: 000877800
timestamp: ::45:354, filepos: 000878800
timestamp: ::48:565, filepos: 00087a000
timestamp: ::51:652, filepos: 00087c000
timestamp: ::53:779, filepos: 00087d000
timestamp: ::55:989, filepos: 00087e800
timestamp: ::59:159, filepos: 00087f800
timestamp: ::02:704, filepos: 000881000
timestamp: ::04:581, filepos: 000882800
timestamp: ::06:792, filepos: 000884000
timestamp: ::15:509, filepos: 000885000
timestamp: ::20:097, filepos: 000886000
timestamp: ::22:933, filepos: 000887000
timestamp: ::26:478, filepos: 000888000
timestamp: ::30:107, filepos: 000889800
timestamp: ::34:486, filepos: 00088b800
timestamp: ::38:073, filepos: 00088d000
timestamp: ::41:618, filepos: 00088e800
timestamp: ::43:912, filepos: 00088f800
timestamp: ::46:540, filepos: 000891800
timestamp: ::50:586, filepos: 000893800
timestamp: ::54:298, filepos: 000895000
timestamp: ::58:051, filepos: 000896800
timestamp: :::638, filepos: 000898000
timestamp: ::05:392, filepos: 00089a000
timestamp: ::08:895, filepos: 00089b800
timestamp: ::12:649, filepos: 00089d000
timestamp: ::16:236, filepos: 00089e000
timestamp: ::19:448, filepos: 00089f800
timestamp: ::23:118, filepos: 0008a1800
timestamp: ::27:497, filepos: 0008a4000
timestamp: ::30:1, filepos: 0008a6000
timestamp: ::32:836, filepos: 0008a8800
timestamp: ::36:6, filepos: 0008ab800
timestamp: ::39:134, filepos: 0008ad800
timestamp: ::42:929, filepos: 0008b0000
timestamp: ::46:266, filepos: 0008b2800
timestamp: ::48:185, filepos: 0008b3800
timestamp: ::55:692, filepos: 0008b4000
timestamp: ::10:540, filepos: 0008b6800
timestamp: ::12:542, filepos: 0008b7000
timestamp: ::18:131, filepos: 0008b8000
timestamp: ::19:966, filepos: 0008b9800
timestamp: ::21:843, filepos: 0008bb800
timestamp: ::23:637, filepos: 0008bc000
timestamp: ::25:514, filepos: 0008bd000
timestamp: ::37:150, filepos: 0008be800
timestamp: ::41:071, filepos: 0008bf000
timestamp: ::42:864, filepos: 0008bf800
timestamp: ::49:996, filepos: 0008c0800
timestamp: ::53:792, filepos: 0008c1800
timestamp: ::07:180, filepos: 0008c4000
timestamp: ::09:224, filepos: 0008c4800
timestamp: ::11:810, filepos: 0008c5000
timestamp: ::25:699, filepos: 0008c6000
timestamp: ::42:591, filepos: 0008c7000
timestamp: ::54:561, filepos: 0008c7800
timestamp: ::23:632, filepos: 0008c8000
timestamp: ::27:969, filepos: 0008c9800
timestamp: ::29:971, filepos: 0008cb800
timestamp: ::42:067, filepos: 0008cd800
timestamp: ::59:251, filepos: 0008cf000
timestamp: ::07:884, filepos: 0008cf800
timestamp: ::13:306, filepos: 0008d0800
timestamp: ::26:027, filepos: 0008d1800
timestamp: ::28:405, filepos: 0008d2800
timestamp: ::31:575, filepos: 0008d4800
timestamp: ::34:828, filepos: 0008d7000
timestamp: ::36:872, filepos: 0008d8800
timestamp: ::39:374, filepos: 0008d9800
timestamp: ::42:335, filepos: 0008db800
timestamp: ::44:212, filepos: 0008dd000
timestamp: ::47:591, filepos: 0008df800
timestamp: ::51:261, filepos: 0008e2000
timestamp: ::53:096, filepos: 0008e3800
timestamp: ::54:931, filepos: 0008e5800
timestamp: ::57:767, filepos: 0008e7000
timestamp: ::00:979, filepos: 0008e8800
timestamp: ::03:607, filepos: 0008eb000
timestamp: ::06:902, filepos: 0008ec000
timestamp: ::09:613, filepos: 0008ed800
timestamp: ::12:073, filepos: 0008ef800
timestamp: ::15:660, filepos: 0008f1000
timestamp: ::18:580, filepos: 0008f3800
timestamp: ::21:374, filepos: 0008f5000
timestamp: ::25:253, filepos: 0008f7800
timestamp: ::26:963, filepos: 0008f9000
timestamp: ::34:4, filepos: 0008fb800
timestamp: ::36:6, filepos: 0008fc800
timestamp: ::38:391, filepos: 0008fd800
timestamp: ::42:520, filepos: 0008ff000
timestamp: ::45:732, filepos: 0009800
timestamp: :::498, filepos: 000902800
timestamp: ::04:960, filepos: 000904000
timestamp: ::07:379, filepos: 000904800
timestamp: ::16:2, filepos: 000905800
timestamp: ::19:933, filepos: 000906800
timestamp: ::22:978, filepos: 000907800
timestamp: ::39:577, filepos: 000909800
timestamp: ::43:873, filepos: 00090a800
timestamp: ::46:376, filepos: 00090b800
timestamp: ::49:754, filepos: 00090c000
timestamp: ::52:632, filepos: 00090c800
timestamp: ::56:052, filepos: 00090e000
timestamp: ::58:054, filepos: 00090e800
timestamp: ::02:058, filepos: 000911000
timestamp: ::05:854, filepos: 000912000
timestamp: ::08:023, filepos: 000913000
timestamp: ::11:067, filepos: 000913800
timestamp: ::13:194, filepos: 000914800
timestamp: ::15:363, filepos: 000916800
timestamp: ::20:535, filepos: 000917800
timestamp: ::22:871, filepos: 000919000
timestamp: ::26:291, filepos: 00091b800
timestamp: ::34:1, filepos: 00091f800
timestamp: ::39:596, filepos: 000920000
timestamp: ::46:352, filepos: 000921000
timestamp: ::48:855, filepos: 000923000
timestamp: ::52:734, filepos: 000924800
timestamp: ::59:908, filepos: 000925800
timestamp: ::03:828, filepos: 000926800
timestamp: ::07:082, filepos: 000927800
timestamp: ::08:917, filepos: 000928000
timestamp: ::10:919, filepos: 000929800
timestamp: ::16:007, filepos: 00092a000
timestamp: ::21:197, filepos: 00092a800
timestamp: ::23:491, filepos: 00092d000
timestamp: ::25:493, filepos: 000930000
timestamp: ::27:495, filepos: 000932000
timestamp: ::32:542, filepos: 000935800
timestamp: ::36:921, filepos: 000938800
timestamp: ::39:924, filepos: 00093b000
timestamp: ::44:846, filepos: 00093e800
timestamp: ::47:265, filepos: 00093f800
timestamp: ::17:795, filepos: 000940800
timestamp: ::22:133, filepos: 000941800
timestamp: ::26:262, filepos: 000943000
timestamp: ::29:515, filepos: 000944800
timestamp: ::33:436, filepos: 000947800
timestamp: ::37:7, filepos: 000948800
timestamp: ::39:108, filepos: 000949800
timestamp: ::43:488, filepos: 00094a000
timestamp: ::47:825, filepos: 00094c000
timestamp: ::49:744, filepos: 00094d000
timestamp: ::52:330, filepos: 00094e000
timestamp: ::54:999, filepos: 000950800
timestamp: ::58:836, filepos: 000952000
timestamp: ::00:922, filepos: 000953000
timestamp: ::02:692, filepos: 000954000
timestamp: ::16:414, filepos: 000955800
timestamp: ::20:793, filepos: 000956000
timestamp: ::28:134, filepos: 000957000
timestamp: ::45:109, filepos: 000958000
timestamp: ::49:739, filepos: 000959800
timestamp: ::51:741, filepos: 00095a000
timestamp: ::56:0, filepos: 00095b800
timestamp: :::459, filepos: 00095d000
timestamp: ::05:963, filepos: 00095d800
timestamp: ::10:676, filepos: 00095e800
timestamp: ::21:646, filepos: 00095f800
timestamp: ::32:448, filepos: 000962000
timestamp: ::34:117, filepos: 000963000
timestamp: ::36:619, filepos: 000964800
timestamp: ::39:622, filepos: 000967000
timestamp: ::41:749, filepos: 000968800
timestamp: ::45:420, filepos: 00096a800
timestamp: ::48:005, filepos: 00096c800
timestamp: ::50:550, filepos: 00096f000
timestamp: ::54:262, filepos: 000971800
timestamp: ::57:265, filepos: 000974000
timestamp: ::31:716, filepos: 000977000
timestamp: ::22:683, filepos: 000978800
timestamp: ::24:685, filepos: 00097a800
timestamp: ::28:064, filepos: 00097c000
timestamp: ::37:198, filepos: 00097d000
timestamp: ::39:784, filepos: 00097e800
timestamp: ::42:245, filepos: 000980000
timestamp: ::44:247, filepos: 000981000
timestamp: ::46:415, filepos: 000982800
timestamp: ::50:086, filepos: 000984800
timestamp: ::52:880, filepos: 000985800
timestamp: ::58:386, filepos: 000988000
timestamp: ::04:225, filepos: 00098a000
timestamp: ::10:022, filepos: 00098b800
timestamp: ::15:444, filepos: 00098d800
timestamp: ::18:781, filepos: 00098f000
timestamp: ::20:783, filepos: 000990800
timestamp: ::27:164, filepos: 000991800
timestamp: ::29:792, filepos: 000992800
timestamp: ::32:670, filepos: 000994800
timestamp: ::35:464, filepos: 000997000
timestamp: ::37:758, filepos: 000999000
timestamp: :::596, filepos: 00099b000
timestamp: ::43:514, filepos: 00099d800
timestamp: ::46:892, filepos: 0009a0000
timestamp: ::49:312, filepos: 0009a1800
timestamp: ::53:9, filepos: 0009a3800
timestamp: ::56:736, filepos: 0009a7000
timestamp: ::59:405, filepos: 0009aa000
timestamp: :::657, filepos: 0009ac800
timestamp: ::03:826, filepos: 0009ae800
timestamp: ::06:787, filepos: 0009b0000
timestamp: ::15:963, filepos: 0009b1000
timestamp: ::19:300, filepos: 0009b3000
timestamp: ::23:137, filepos: 0009b4800
timestamp: ::26:891, filepos: 0009b6000
timestamp: ::30:311, filepos: 0009b7800
timestamp: ::34:732, filepos: 0009b8800
timestamp: ::38:027, filepos: 0009ba000
timestamp: ::41:822, filepos: 0009bb800
timestamp: ::45:660, filepos: 0009bd000
timestamp: ::49:413, filepos: 0009be800
timestamp: ::56:545, filepos: 0009bf800
timestamp: ::00:049, filepos: 0009c1000
timestamp: ::04:053, filepos: 0009c2000
timestamp: ::07:473, filepos: 0009c3800
timestamp: ::12:395, filepos: 0009c4800
timestamp: ::14:355, filepos: 0009c6000
timestamp: ::18:359, filepos: 0009c7800
timestamp: ::26:867, filepos: 0009c8800
timestamp: ::30:287, filepos: 0009cb000
timestamp: ::33:624, filepos: 0009cd800
timestamp: ::36:961, filepos: 0009d0000
timestamp: ::40:506, filepos: 0009d2800
timestamp: :::968, filepos: 0009d5000
timestamp: ::48:764, filepos: 0009d7800
timestamp: ::51:934, filepos: 0009d9800
timestamp: ::55:521, filepos: 0009db800
timestamp: ::02:194, filepos: 0009dd800
timestamp: ::05:656, filepos: 0009df800
timestamp: ::09:243, filepos: 0009e1800
timestamp: ::15:583, filepos: 0009e3800
timestamp: ::22:423, filepos: 0009e5800
timestamp: ::29:805, filepos: 0009e8000
timestamp: ::33:058, filepos: 0009ea000
timestamp: ::36:687, filepos: 0009ec000
timestamp: ::42:318, filepos: 0009ee000
timestamp: ::45:738, filepos: 0009f0800
timestamp: ::50:159, filepos: 0009f3000
timestamp: ::11:806, filepos: 0009f4800
timestamp: ::15:142, filepos: 0009f6800
timestamp: ::19:188, filepos: 0009f8000
timestamp: ::22:650, filepos: 0009fa000
timestamp: ::26:028, filepos: 0009fc800
timestamp: ::29:782, filepos: 0009fe000
timestamp: ::34:2, filepos: 0009ff800
timestamp: ::37:665, filepos: 000a800
timestamp: ::41:585, filepos: 000a04000
timestamp: ::48:259, filepos: 000a06800
timestamp: ::51:3, filepos: 000a08000
timestamp: ::55:599, filepos: 000a09800
timestamp: ::58:227, filepos: 000a0b000
timestamp: ::03:566, filepos: 000a0c800
timestamp: ::07:695, filepos: 000a0d800
timestamp: ::16:203, filepos: 000a0e800
timestamp: ::20:249, filepos: 000a10800
timestamp: ::24:545, filepos: 000a13000
timestamp: ::26:547, filepos: 000a14000
timestamp: ::28:674, filepos: 000a15800
timestamp: ::33:888, filepos: 000a18000
timestamp: ::36:473, filepos: 000a19000
timestamp: ::41:061, filepos: 000a1b000
timestamp: ::44:398, filepos: 000a1d800
timestamp: ::47:234, filepos: 000a1f000
timestamp: ::49:528, filepos: 000a20800
timestamp: ::53:115, filepos: 000a23000
timestamp: ::57:536, filepos: 000a25000
timestamp: ::00:915, filepos: 000a27800
timestamp: ::03:751, filepos: 000a29000
timestamp: ::06:086, filepos: 000a2a800
timestamp: ::09:924, filepos: 000a2d000
timestamp: ::12:760, filepos: 000a2f000
timestamp: ::27:274, filepos: 000a30800